







Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

Summary

Last Active: 18-Jan-21

Jump to Section

I am looking for a challenging role in a reputable organization to utilize my technical and management skills to grow the organization and enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in the IT sector. 15+ Years of total experience as Unix Admin whereas worked as a Unix cum Team Lead for five years for Royal Mail Group and National Grid accounts. I do have a firm grasp of Cloud Computing SaaS, PaaS, laaS fundamentals experience, and Legacy Datacenter Operations model

Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Work Experience

HCL Technologies as Associate Consultant Nov 2020 to Till Date

Linux/Ansible/Cloud

Tech Mahindra Limited as Sr. Technical Associate Dec 2008 to Aug 2010

Manage the environments as a team Infrastructure Lead. Experience in Infrastructure Development and Operations. Strong Experience on Solaris/Linux platform. Manage Data Centre Operations (Production, Development and Staging & DR) & Security/Firewall for business management and recovery practices. Manage the environments as a team Infrastructure CONSULTANT & Troubleshooting L3 issues. Maintain, manage and Administration huge number of Solaris, Linux, and AlX Servers. Set up and maintain virtual environments Solaris Zones, RHEV, Wware.

Satyam Computer Services as Engineer - Networking Apr 2007 to Dec 2008

Managing the baseline support. Maintain, manage and administer large number of Solaris & Linux servers for all environments (including Production, development, TST, QA, Staging, and DR) hosting critical business applications and databases for Merrill Lynch. Provide issue resolution from India on a 24x7 model of all Solaris, Linux and TSM Backup related tickets. Troubleshoot High Severity issues with regards to Solaris/Linux

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Magadh University in 2002

PG: MBA/PGDM (Information Technology) from Institute of Management Technology (IMT), Chaziabad in 2013

^ Back to Top

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Linux	5, 6, 7	2020	10 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Ansible		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Shell / Python Scripting		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
VMWARE		2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Qlik Sense Desktop Tool		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Version Control		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
ITIL		2020	13 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
AWS Cloud		2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Solaris	9, 10	2016	7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
VCS		2016	7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - IClClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.